GNOME 3.26 is here..
..packed by 6 months of exciting changes by the community.
The shell is GNOME's user interface..
..and this cycle it has received a visual overhaul of its search,..
..giving you a better overview.
GNOME's interface is configured from the control center,..
..which features a new sidebar.
..making it possible to jump between settings easily..
..to find what you are looking for.
A dedicated Wi-Fi area ensures easy..
..and logical access for managing wireless connections.
The Display settings are quicker to access,..
..so you can configure common setups..
.. such as single displays, joint displays and mirror.
Many improvements have also landed for GNOME Apps.
Simple Scan has had a redesign of its editing tools.
Polari now comes with an initial setup to get you started quickly..
..and has support for sending and receiving emojis.
Logs gained event compression for better overview.
Photos has new zoom controls,..
..and Disks gained the ability to resize partitions..
..and new disk image files.
Developers can look forward to big additions in Builder.
It features a new visual design and animations.
An initial built-in debugger enables you..
..to debug application threads and add break points.
..and much more.
GNOME is a worldwide project..
..and with your help we can push software freedom to the next level.
Have a chat with us or read more at gnome.org.